<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zooma</string>
    <string name="kisah_gajah_dan_semut_title">
        The Story of the Elephant and the Ant
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_gajah_dan_semut_text">
        Once upon a time, a small ant and a large elephant lived in the forest. This big elephant is very strong and is known to get angry easily with small things. He also often underestimated every other small animal that lived in the forest.
        Somewhere in the forest, there was a small ant who lived with his family in a deep tree hole. The ant is known to be kind and hardworking. Every day, this little ant and his family go in search of food.
        Often, they also encounter elephants on their way foraging for food.

        Whenever this ant family encounters an elephant, the elephant will make fun of the ants and annoy them. The giant elephant was very proud of its strength and body. He always uses his power to make the ants angry. All the members of the ant family were worried about the elephants joke.
        One fine morning, when the little ant and his family went to look for food, the elephant squirted water from its trunk at the ant family. This incident shocked the entire ant family and the little ant started to cry.
        The ant asked him, “Hey! Whats wrong with you? Why do you keep bothering us?"
        Seeing the ant crying, the elephant said angrily, "Stop crying or I will crush you to death."
        The poor little ant stopped crying, but he decided to teach the giant elephant a lesson.

        Another ant said, “You mustnt fight with the elephant, he is very angry and very strong! He can destroy you." However, the tough ant replied, “Hmmm… Something needs to be done about it.”
        The next day when the ant was going to work, the little ant decided to teach the elephant a lesson. He quietly climbed the elephants body and walked until it got into the elephants trunk!
        Once inside, he started biting the elephant.
        The elephant shouted, “Aaah! It hurts!"
        The elephant tried everything but couldnt get the ants to stop biting him or come out of his trunk.

        The elephant shouted again, “Aaah! Please stop it! Stop it right now!" There was nothing he could do to get the ant out of its trunk, until the elephant finally felt tired.
        The ant replied from within its trunk, "Well, I hope you now know how other living things feel when you hurt them."
        "Yes I know! Please stop now!” said the elephant begging the ant
        "In that case, okay." said the ant as it stopped biting it and came out of its trunk.
        The elephant was finally relieved, and he also apologized to the ant, “Sorry! I now understand how it feels to be bullied. I promise Ill never do it again."
        From that day on, the elephant promised not to disturb any creatures in the forest. And this is how the giant elephant learns. After that, all the creatures in the forest lived happily ever after.
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_kuda_dan_keledai_title">
        The Story of the Horse and the Donkey
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_kuda_dan_keledai_text">
        Once upon a time, there lived a very diligent washing man. The man lived in a very simple house, where there was a stable of horses and donkeys behind his house.
        "Yesterday was a tiring day," said the horse to the donkey.
        “The horse, it was me who was so tired. I brought all the laundry," answered the donkey.
        "Maybe, but I was ridden by the washerwoman," replied the horse again.
        While they were chatting, the washerman came to the stable to send the horses and donkeys to work again.

        Every morning the horses and donkeys worked to help the washing man. The washerwoman would put all her clothes on a donkey and ride a horse to go to a faraway village to bring back her laundry.
        All day long he delivered clean clothes to everyone, then picked up the dirty laundry back. But the donkey often felt tired, because he had brought all the clothes.
        One day, the donkey was so tired he didnt want to eat and fell asleep.
        “What are you doing donkey, you want to sleep again? ha ha ha. I can even run around in this stable," mocked the horse to the donkey.
        "Of course you can, because you didnt bring all the dirty laundry," replied the donkey curtly.

        The next day, the washerman got up early to wash all the dirty clothes he picked up yesterday.
        Then the washerman called his horse and donkey to get ready to go to the village. As usual, the donkey brought all the clothes to be delivered.
        The washerwoman knocked door after door in the village to pick up dirty clothes. On that day he took a lot of dirty clothes, almost more than fifteen houses. Then he put all the dirty clothes on the back of his poor donkey.
        The donkey felt very tired, he felt that his burden that day was very heavy.

        On that day, the washerman walked beside the donkey, to lighten his load a little. Unfortunately the poor donkey couldnt stand up anymore, so he fell down sitting in the middle of the road.
        When the washerman realized that his donkey was tired, he decided to lie down for a while under a tree and rest.”
        "Hey," called the donkey, staring at the horse.
        "What do you want?" replied the horse curtly.
        "I just want to say, today my luggage is too heavy not like usual. Can you help me a little bit?” asked the donkey to the horse.
        "Im sorry donkey, but its not my job to carry laundry" replied the horse casually and immediately left the donkey.

        After resting for a while, the washerman continued his journey. Because he was still tired, he just walked a few steps and the donkey fell back.
        The washerwoman realized that the donkey was very tired, so he gave the donkey a drink. So that the donkey would not get tired, he transferred all the laundry that the donkey had brought onto the horses back.
        The donkey finally felt better, but the horse objected. From then on, it was the horse that carried all the dirty laundry. So tired, the horse can not eat while in the stable.
        "Today I was too selfish to you my friend, forgive me" said the horse to the donkey.
        “Now that you understand, helping and sharing is very important. Dont forget that, my friend."
        From then on, the washerman always shared his dirty clothes with the horse, the donkey, and himself. So, neither party feels disadvantaged, and the work feels lighter.
        Such is the fairy tale of the horse and the donkey. From the fairy tale above, it can be concluded that our fellow living beings must act fairly and help each other.
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_kucing_dan_rubah_title">
        The Story of the Cat and the Fox
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_kucing_dan_rubah_text">
        Once, there was a cat and a fox who traveled together. While traveling, they both hunt fat rats or chickens here and there, and every time they eat, they often chat and argue. And sometimes their arguments make one of them angry.
        "You think youre very clever huh?" said the Fox. "Or are you just being ignorant? Because I feel like I know more tricks than you!"
        The Cat replied with an angry tone, "I admit, I only mastered one trick, but with this one trick, frankly I say, is worth a thousand times better than your tricks!"
        Before long, they heard the trumpet of the hunter and the bark of the hound. In an instant, the Cat climbed up the tree and hid among the dense leaves.
        "This is my trick," he said to the Fox. "Now show me your precious tricks."
        Although the Fox had many plans for his escape, he could not determine which plans and tricks he would try first. When the hunting dog was close, he tried to dodge here and there. Then he hastened his run, and hid into the hole, but all in vain. The hunting dogs managed to catch him.
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_ayam_jago_sombong_title">
        The Story of a Arrogant Rooster
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_ayam_jago_sombong_text">
        Once upon a time in the forest lived a rooster. Her fur is very beautiful. Red, yellow and black. On top of his head was a pink squiggly comb. His crowing voice is very melodious. Every morning he always crowed to wake the forest dwellers.
        The rooster was very proud of his voice. Wherever he goes and meets other animals he always shows his beautiful fur and makes his long, melodious crow. "In this forest I am the animal that has a beautiful voice," said the rooster in his heart. The rooster was getting more and more proud day by day. The animals he met he always insulted and insulted.
        One day, this rooster perched on a tree near the lake. That is the only lake in the forest. If you want a drink, forest dwellers go to the lake, especially if you want to swim, forest dwellers must go to this lake. At that time a duck was about to swim in the lake. The chicken that saw the duck said hello. "Hey duck where are you going? Duck looks up at the tree. "Oh chicken, apparently, I want to swim" replied the duck. "Ah duck... you can swim, look at me, can fly, perch on a tree and have a sweet voice." The rooster keeps saying badmouthing the duck, you duck is nothing to me. "Youre weird, its your turn to eat fast and beg for mercy, but when you walk youre waddling, slow, ah... you suck at duck, ha...-ha.....ha..., the roosters laughter broke out. .
        The humiliated duck is sad. "I know you have beautiful feathers and voice, but you cant swim like me," replied the duck. " ah.. swim you say, who said I cant...! its easy," said the rooster. Come on, lets have a swimming competition," challenged the rooster to the duck.
        "Well then," said the duck. It would be nice if the forest dwellers knew we were in a swimming competition," said the rooster. "Yes, well, we will tell the forest dwellers so that tomorrow they will watch us compete," replied the duck.
        The next day the forest dwellers were at the edge of the lake. They were enthusiastic to see the swimming waves between roosters and ducks. As the referee appointed deer.
        Mouse Deer called the two contestants to get ready on the edge of the lake. The mouse deer counted, “one...two...three...jump!
        The duck first jumped into the lake, he quickly swam to the end of the lake. The rooster jumped. "jburrrr....plaque...plaque...plaque" the sound of a roosters wings. The roosters body swayed to the left and slowly his body sank now only his head was still sticking out of the water. He couldnt take it anymore, he almost drowned. The rooster screamed. " Help! help". The duck who was already in the middle of the lake saw the chicken almost drowning, he immediately turned back and saved the chicken and took him to the edge of the lake.
        Ukh...ukh...ukh" the mouth of the rooster let out water. He had apparently swallowed a lot of water. I cant swim, said the rooster. "Yes ... answered the duck briefly. "You must understand that we should not be arrogant with what we have". Each of us has advantages and disadvantages, continued the duck. "Eat me, I was wrong" said the rooster. You ducks are great. Since then the chicken no longer boasts in front of other animals.
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_harimau_dan_kancil_title">
        The story of the tiger and the mouse deer
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_harimau_dan_kancil_text">
        One day the deer met a tiger while playing in the mountains. Without a doubt, the tiger thought the mouse deer would be his delicious lunch. However, the mouse deer had apparently seen the appearance of the tiger and pretended to be calm while saying, “Tiger, you are very handsome. Your head, face, body and legs are all so perfect and there is no match in this forest. Unfortunately, your tail is so ugly it cant keep up with your other prowess."

        The tiger was eaten by the deers instigation and felt that what he said was right, so he asked the deer, "How can I make my tail beautiful?" The mouse deer then looked around the tigers tail, as if examining it, and told the tiger, "If you can make it straight, your tail will look very beautiful."

        "So how can I straighten it out?" asked the tiger.

        “Hmm, its actually not that difficult. Im just not sure if youd dare to do it or not."

        "Theres nothing that Im afraid of," said the tiger who planned to straighten his tail first before he ate the deer. Then, he urged the mouse deer, "Quick! Help me straighten my tail!”

        The mouse deer quickly gathered nine bundles of pine needles, then tied the tigers tail to the tree while burning the pine needles. The tiger felt hot because it had to withstand the fire. As a result, the hair all over his body even burned out. The tiger was angry, "You really are a stupid mouse deer! My tail does look straight, but you have burned my clothes. I wont forgive you!"

        Instead of being scared, the mouse deer calmly replied, "Dont worry. I will give you a new one,"

        "You have fooled me," continued the tiger.

        "Im serious. However, you better wash yourself thoroughly before you put on new clothes,"

        "Wheres the water?"

        "There," the tiger, which was already burned and badly injured, couldnt wait to follow the deer to find water. However, unfortunate for the tiger, the mouse deer took him to the area where the hungry crocodiles were waiting. The crocodiles immediately pounced on the tiger, which now has no hair and has been seriously injured.

        The tiger believed the words of the mouse deer and dropped his own dignity and position. As a result of his wrong decision, not only did he fail to get Kancil as his lunch, but also had to close his life history in an unfortunate way.
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_sapi_dan_kerbau_title">
        The Story of the Cow and the Buffalo
    </string>
    <string name="kisah_sapi_dan_kerbau_text">
       Al the story in ancient times when cows and buffalo were still friends. At that time the cow had a slightly brownish black skin color. While the buffalo skin is white.

        It is said that one day in a green meadow, there came a newcomer, the newcomer was a bull with big and pointed horns. And with dark black skin color made the bull look very dashing. So the cows in the meadow admired the bull very much.
        Long story short, very quickly. Rumors of the bulls valor quickly spread to all corners of the prairie. And the bull became the prima donna and the byword of the cows and buffaloes in the meadow. The bull who has a slightly brownish black skin color does not really care about the news that has become a byword, he is grateful for the gift that God has given him.

        But not so with the Buffalo. He is even jealous and very jealous of the bull who is the prima donna and idolized by the females.

        "The bull, whats so great about him? I am also the same as him, he has big and pointed horns, my body also looks dashing and big, only the skin color is different, the bull is the prima donna...." Looks like the bull was grumbling to himself

        "Hmmmmmmm..... maybe if my skin color was black, I would definitely be more manly than the bull, and I would also be famous, in fact Im more famous than the bull, mmmmmm" the buffalo grumbled again

        "Oh yes, I have a great idea to make my skin color Black. But will the cow want to exchange skin with me? Well, I have a good idea to trick the cow into wanting to exchange skin with me, haaaaaaa" grumbled the buffalo while slightly smile

        Finally Sikerbau came to meet the cow who was soaking in the river. Seen the buffalo began to carry out his cunning idea, he also began to persuade the cow to want to exchange skins. But the cow didnt want to because he was grateful for what God had given him.
        But the buffalo did not want to give up, he kept on persuading the cow so that he would change the skin. Until the buffalo whined asking for a request in the name of friendship to the sisapi.

        Due to constant pressure, the cow finally felt sorry for the buffalo and the cow wanted to exchange skins with the buffalo.
        However, the cow gave a condition to the buffalo, the buffalo had to promise that if he had exchanged skins, the buffalo had to be grateful for whatever he had.
        And without thinking again, the buffalo also agreed to the conditions proposed by the cow. Because the buffalo has been carried away by lust.

        Finally they both exchanged skins, the cow became white while the buffalo was black and slightly brown.

        However, after they exchanged skins, apparently there was a problem, it turned out that the leather of the cow was too small for the size of a large and stocky buffalo. So that the skin feels tight in wearing it, too tight and makes the buffalo uncomfortable wearing it.

        While the buffalo skin worn by the cow is too big, even the neck looks slack and feels very loose, making the cow feel free to move.

        Because he felt uncomfortable with the buffalo with his new skin, Sikerbau again invited the cow to exchange skins again. However, the cow did not want to exchange skins anymore, because the buffalo had promised and agreed to the conditions given by the cow to him.

        Repeatedly the buffalo was whining to change the skin back, but the cow still did not want to.

        In fact, whenever they meet wherever and whenever, the buffalo is still trying to persuade the cow to exchange its hide back. But the cow always said "Moohh (I dont want)"    
    </string>
</resources>